prezly.com 2016-03-15

# Privacy Policy - Prezly

#### Last Updated: March 26, 2015

### Protecting Your Privacy

We believe in protecting your privacy. We've put together this privacy policy to explain how your information is protected, stored, and used. By using the service, you consent to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy and are aware that our policies may evolve in the future.

We may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will revise the “last updated” date given above. It is your responsibility to review this Policy frequently and to remain informed of any changes to them. The then-current version of these Terms will supersede all earlier versions.

### Data collection from visitors of Press Room(s)

_This section describes our policies for internet users that visit Press Rooms hosted on Prezly._

In the course of providing user and usage data analytics Services to our customers, Prezly collects both non-personally identifiable and personally identifiable information about end users of Press Rooms. Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) collected by Prezly includes data such as your name, address, phone number, or email address, which you have provided to the Customer. Prezly will not collect your password for any Press Room or credit card information. We do not purchase or receive information about you from third parties (other than our customers).

Prezly also collects non-personally identifiable information about you from Press Rooms you visit, including the following types of data: Standard Data – common information found in every communication sent over the internet. Using this information, information such as browser type (e.g., Chrome or Internet Explorer); operating system (e.g,. Macintosh or Windows); browser language (e.g., Java or Unix); and internet service provider (e.g., Verizon Fios or AOL) Clickstream Data – how you use our Press Rooms and various pages on the internet. Prezly may use this PII and non-personally identifiable information to provide our Services to our customers.

#### Use of Cookies

Cookies are identifiers transferred to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our Press Room are visited and by how many people. Like most internet sites, Prezly uses cookies to enhance our visitors’ and customers’ experience on the internet. Most browsers allow you to prevent the browser from accepting new cookies, to be notified when you receive a new cookie, or to disable cookies. 

#### Retention of Data

Cookies set on behalf of Prezly expire after three years and the expiration date updates every time you encounter our server. Prezly retains standard web log data, aggregations and reports, visitor details for up to 10 years after you visit a Customer Site.

#### Access to your Data

Please get in touch via [help@prezly.com](mailto:help@prezly.com) if you want get access, make changes or request removal of the data Prezly collected about you.

### Data Collection from Prezly Customers

_This section describes our policies for end users of the Prezly homepage (https://www.prezly.com) and Prezly Backend (https://rock.prezly.com), Prezly customers, and corporate partners._

#### Data You Provide

We receive and store any information you enter on the Homepage or through the Backend or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use PII provided by you for such purposes as responding to your requests for Services, customizing the content you see, communicating with you about our products, and marketing our Services to you. In order for you to use all of our features, you must register with Prezly. We require your e-mail address and password during the registration process. Further information may be required if you choose to purchase paid components of the Services, such as credit card and billing information. Prezly uses third party partners for credit card processing who may require and store your credit card and billing information.

#### Automatic tracking

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Prezly automatically receives and records “traffic data” on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and pages you request. Prezly uses this traffic data to analyze trends and administer the Site. Our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Site and its components. This data is only used in the aggregate. This type of collective data enables us to figure out how often users use different parts of the Site and Services. In addition, we may provide statistical collective user information, not information about you personally, to our partners so that they understand how often people use specific components of our Site and Services.

#### E-mail and In-App Communications

If you purchase the Services, Prezly will communicate with you about the services you purchase by e-mail. You consent to receiving such confirmations by e-mail or via In-App mesasges. If you contact us via e-mail through the Site, we may retain a record of your contact information and any information you provide us in your message to respond to you. We may receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail from Prezly. We may also send e-mails with service updates, news or promotions. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, please contact us at [help@prezly.com](mailto:help@prezly.com).

#### Information From Other Sources

To improve our Services, we may receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. Like the information you provide to us, we do not share this information with anyone except authorized third parties in connection with providing you with our Services.

#### Cookies

Cookies are identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our Site are visited and by how many people. Most browsers allow you to prevent the browser from accepting new cookies, to be notified when you receive a new cookie, or to disable cookies. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our Site. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

### Sharing of Personal Identified Information

_This section describes our policies for sharing PII received from either Press Room visitors or Prezly Homepage visitors or Prezly customers.We neither rent nor sell PII to anyone. Except as provided for in any additional agreement you enter into with Prezly, we maintain the confidentiality of your PII and share your PII only as described below:_

#### Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control

Prezly may provide services or sell products jointly with affiliated businesses. We will share customer information that is related to such transactions with those affiliated businesses. We require our affiliates to provide the same level of privacy protection that we do and they do not have the right to share or use PII for any purpose other than for an authorized transaction. Prezly may share aggregated demographic information with customers in connection with the provision of the Services.

#### Agents

We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products and services. Examples include billing, processing payments, providing marketing assistance, and providing customer service. Our agents subscribe to the same level of privacy protection as we do. Unless we tell you differently, Prezly does not share, and Agents do not have any right to use PII collected from our Site and Services beyond what is necessary to assist us. Financial and billing information is collected through the Site and Services directly by a third-party intermediary and is used solely to bill for the Services. Prezly does not receive your billing information from this third-party intermediary, who may store, retain, and use the information provided solely for the purpose of credit card processing.

#### Promotional Offers

We may send offers to our customers on behalf of other businesses or provide our customers with the opportunity to notify end users directly of promotions by text messages or e-mail. If you do not wish to receive these offers, please e-mail us at [help@prezly.com](mailto:help@prezly.com).

#### Business Transfers

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Prezly, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is reviewed and transferred. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Prezly may continue to use your PII as set forth in this policy.

#### Protection

We may release PII when we in our sole discretion believe in good faith that release is necessary or appropriate to comply with the law, enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements, or protect the rights, property, or safety of Prezly, our employees, our customers, or others.

#### Your Consent

Except as set forth above, we will not share PII collected from Prezly customers or end users with third parties without your consent.

### Additional Policies

#### Security

Your Prezly account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. We use industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software to protect the security of your PII during transmission, which encrypts all of the information you input. Only employees or agents who need personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices.

#### Accessing Information

You are able to access, add to and update certain information about you. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. You may deactivate your Prezly account by following the deactivation process set forth on the Site. Some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account. Please contact us at [help@prezly.com](mailto:help@prezly.com) if you have questions or concerns about accessing your PII.

#### Conditions of Use

Your use of the Site and Services and any possible dispute over privacy are subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, including limitations on damages, dispute resolution, and application of the Belgian law and competence of the Belgian courts.

#### International Visitors

For users outside the European Union, please note that any data or PII you enter into the Services or Site will be transferred out of your country and into the EU. You consent to such transfer through your use of the Services and Site. You also warrant that you have the right to transfer such information outside your country and into the EU.

#### Use by Children

Prezly is not intended for children. If you are under 18, you may use the Site and Services only with the supervision of your parent or guardian.

#### Third Party Sites

The Site and Services may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the Site or Services. These other websites are not under Prezly’s control and Customer.io is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.
